Catarina Claes's
glamorous summer vacation
Part 1
Summer vacation is here!
Thus far, I've been successful
at avoiding my doom flags,
but I can't get careless now.
My latest creation.
This looks perfect!
Thanks, Tom-san!
How was that?!
Um... What in the world...
I'm practicing throwing toy
snakes as if they were real!
If it becomes necessary,
I can do this to make him drop his guard!
And when would that become necessary?
It'll be necessary when it's necessary!
Just tell me whether it looks natural or not.
HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 6
I Had Fun Over Summer Vacation...
I just love summer vacation.
With all this free time, I can do things I enjoy.
And throwing toys around is
one of the things you enjoy?
Don't play around too much.
Remember, we have homework, as well.
I'll have to work the fields next!
Lady Catarina.
I baked these sweets.
Would you care to have some?
Wow, thanks!
I haven't had your homemade sweets in so long!
It's delicious!
Thank you for looking after Catarina at school.
I'm sure it's been challenging.
No, not at all.
She changed drastically
after she took hat bump to the head as a child.
She was a selfish brat before,
and now she's a troublemaker.
But many things have changed as a result.
For example, the head maid,
Joana-san, and the gardener, Tom-san.
They never opened up to anyone before,
but they seem to enjoy themselves
so much with Lady Catarina.
That goes for me, as well.
That's true.
It's because of her
Me and my husband can speak speak honestly with each other now.
She's made the entire Claes
household a brighter—
Heave-ho!
She's made the entire household a bri—
And here we go!
She's made the—
Heave-ho and here we go!
Heave-ho and—
Catarina!
Stop belting out those outlandish yells!
Catarina Claes's
glamorous summer vacation
Part 2
This year's watermelons
were as sweet and delicious as last year's, right?
Yes, they were.
The breeze feels so nice. It's making me sleepy.
Please, Sister. If you fall asleep out here,
Mother will scold you again.
That's fine.
The grass is really comfy.
Why don't you try it, too?
I'll pass.
Aww...
Keith!
Come on, hurry up! Race you to that tree!
Wait!
Keith?
Monster...
Monster!
Just get out of here!
Mistress's child!
Why are you even here? You're a pest!
Go away already!
Keith?
Just disappear!
What's wrong, Keith?
Are you okay?
Yeah... I just had a scary dream.
Oh... You were moaning a lot.
Sorry for worrying you.
It's okay, Keith.
If you have any more scary dreams, I'll wake you up!
Okay.
I never had any more nightmares after that.
All because she was there for me.
I want some agar jelly noodles.
Huh?
Wh-What does that mean?
Agar jelly noodles are the best in summer!
Or... don't you have them in this world?
You're saying stuff that
makes no sense again...
Catarina Claes's
glamorous summer vacation
Part 3
It's another hot day...
Hi, Catarina.
Geordo-sama.
Would you like to go cool off at the lake?
It sure has been hot every day, hasn't it?
It sure has.
He's sitting awfully close to
be complaining about the heat...
Why did we stop?
Sorry!
Keith?!
Sister, are you okay?
What do you mean?
I'm just going to the lake with Geordo-sama, that's all.
"That's all"?
That's exactly why you're in danger!
Weren't you going to a big social event today?
I did, and I saw Alan-sama there...
Geordo went out by himself.
That's why you came after us?
Yes.
So that's why!
You wanted to come along with us, didn't you?
Oh, gosh! He was lonely because we left him behind!
I thought he'd grown up a lot,
but I guess he's still a child.
Okay, Keith. Why don't you come with us?
Huh?!
Your tenacity really never ceases to amaze me, Keith.
Oh please, it's nothing that special.
They're such good friends.
Oh, I know!
Since we're all here...
It's beautiful!
Yes, it would be the perfect
place for a date, but...
I wasn't expecting this
many people to be here...
I thought it would be even
more fun to invite everyone!
I'm so happy you invited me.
I almost fell a step behind.
I'm happy for a chance to go
on an excursion with you, too.
Yes, truly.
Thank you for bringing me along.
There are boats!
Why don't we ride one together?
Okay!
We don't want anything
happening to you, Sister.
I'll ride with you, too.
I'm afraid we can't do that.
The boat can't carry that many.
Catarina-sama, please ride with me!
It'll be best with two girls!
In that case, I want to ride with you, too!
Me, too!
I believe you're all forgetting
Catarina is engaged to me.
Yes, for now.
And what might that mean?
Oh, nothing.
What are they arguing about?
Yeah, I have no idea, either.
Is riding in a boat really that fun?
Huh?
You don't know how much fun boats are?
I see you're still a child, Alan-sama.
Wh-What?!
We'll have a race to see who can row the fastest!
Victory will depend on arm strength,
so I have a good feeling about this!
In that case, I'd say I have a better chance of winning!
Then why don't we have a showdown, like we used to?
If that's a challenge, I accept!
I've never ridden in a boat before.
Oh, look! There are fish!
How did this happen?
Because we drew lots.
There's no changing the results now.
You're good, for someone
who's never done this before.
You think so?
Well, I can't let her beat me.
See you at the finish, Alan-sama!
Incredible, Catarina-sama! You're amazing!
Delicious!
You really are good at making sweets, Maria-san.
Thank you.
I'm so glad we were all able to get together.
This'll be a fantastic summer vacation memory!
Yes. I think my brother is
having a great time, too.
I can't really see it...
Look closer. He's smiling
just a tiny bit, see?
I can't see it at all...
Hey!
Give that back!
You won't get away!
S-Sister, your skirt!
Worry a little more about who's watching you!
Get back here!
Honestly, that Catarina...
You never used to smile like that.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Even when you smiled on the outside,
you still looked bored.
You might be right.
But isn't the same true for you, Nicol?
You only smile when you're around her.
That's not...
Hold it!
Honestly, she's always leaving herself defenseless...
Keith, just what have they been
teaching her at the Claes home?
I thought she was being taught proper
manners, like everyone else...
Catarina Claes's
glamorous summer vacation
Part 4
Sister, you're going out?
Yes, I'm going shopping with Sophia.
She said the latest book in the
Devilish Count series is out.
For crying out loud!
We've done nothing but play around
since summer vacation started!
Our break should be spent formulating
a strategy to avoid our doom!
Don't you all agree with me?!
Wh-What are you all doing?!
It's summer vacation, so our internal
meetings are on break, too.
I-If we're going to end up doomed anyway,
it might be a good idea to enjoy
this brief respite while we have it.
Yeah, we need a break every now and then.
No objections.
You, too, Chairman?!
Wh-Who are you?
Come and enjoy this vacation with me.
O-Okay!
My favorite bookstore is just ahead.
I can't wait.
Everyone's looking at us.
These beautiful siblings stand out
everywhere they go, don't they?
Hey, I wonder what that shop is.
Want to drop in and see?
Sure!
I bet this would look great on you.
And I think this would look lovely on you.
Really?
Wow! Look at all the romance novels!
There are so many that I haven't heard of.
"A Love Story of a Prince and the
Prince of an Enemy Nation"...
This sounds interesting!
Sounds like it runs pretty deep.
Oh, there it is!
The latest book in the Devilish Count series!
Oh, you're right!
I can't wait to read it!
Isn't it wonderful?
Yes.
Today was so much fun!
It was.
Somehow, I feel as if I spent time
with you like this before, long ago.
Huh? But I don't think we've
ever gone shopping together.
Yes, you're right.
I'm sure it was something I just saw in a dream.
Oh, that's right!
There's something I forgot to buy.
I'm going to go back and get it.
Oh, then I'll go with you.
No, that's all right. I'll have the servant go with me.
You can just wait here with my brother!
Brother! Please do your best!
Bye, now!
W-Wait... Sophia!
There she goes.
Indeed.
Thank you for doing this today.
Huh?
I've never seen Sophia look
so happy while out in town.
Oh, not at all
I had a wonderful time myself.
Catarina Claes...
My sister and I are both
truly happy to have met you.
U-Um... Nicol-sama?
I know I can't wish for it to last forever,
so for just this instant...
Let me stay by your side.
What?!
I'm back!
Wh-What happened?!
The Devilish Count...
Huh?!
Come to think of it, Nicol did
say there was someone he liked.
There's no one alive who wouldn't
fall for that kind of charm.
Catarina Claes's
glamorous summer vacation
Part 5
There are a lot of women here today.
Alan-sama is going to be performing.
Ah, So that's why...
Good evening.
I see you're all here, too.
Good evening, President.
It's nice to see you during our break!
I'm happy to hear you say that.
These are for you, Alan-sama.
That was a wonderful performance.
Oh... Thanks.
That last song was one I hadn't heard before.
Yeah... This was my first time performing that one.
It's called "For You, My Dearest One."
Oh... So you played it with the person you love in mind?
W-Well, yeah, maybe...
But it's not that I love her, exactly...
That reaction...
He definitely had a special someone in mind.
Is it Mary?
Or perhaps Maria?
Alan-sama, the ladies are
waiting for you over there.
Shouldn't you go and see them now?
R-Right... I guess so.
I guess she doesn't like seeing her
fiancé getting so much attention...
Why does she look so serious?!
This is dangerous.
I've spent all these years trying
not to let him realize it...
I'll have to sow some
doubt in him again later.
I can't afford any more competition!
I thought Mary didn't like Alan
that much, unlike in the game,
but maybe her brusque attitude toward
him is just the other side of her love.
I really hope the one Alan
loves is Mary, not Maria!
I've missed being able to see you, Sirius-sama.
Me, too.
I wish summer vacation would end sooner.
Um, excuse me for a moment.
Catarina-san!
You're very popular, President!
Oh... Thanks.
Come to think of it,
you aren't engaged yet, are you?
Well, no.
There have been offers,
but I can't seem to settle on anyone.
Is there already someone you're interested in?
Someone I'm interested in?
Crap! Was it rude to ask him that?!
I-I mean...
No.
Huh?
No, there's no one I'm interested in.
Oh, the dance is about to start.
Your partner is waiting over there, Catarina-san.
R-Right! If you'll excuse me, then...
May I have this dance, Catarina?
Y-Yes.
Let's dance, too, Alan-sama.
R-Right...
Catarina Claes's
glamorous summer vacation
Part 6
Help me, Keith!
I haven't finished this homework
assignment! This one, either!
You haven't even started it!
Every time I asked, you said
you were working on it!
W-Well, I did do a little bit of it!
You mean these two measly lines
you wrote on this one page?!
I'm sorry.
It's partially my fault, too,
for believing you without question.
Ouch, little brother...
Anyway...
We have to go back to school tomorrow,
so you need to get this taken care of today.
I'll help you.
Right...
Sister, I've finished this one.
Thanks, Keith!
I'm almost done, too.
Need help?
I'll be fine. You can go to bed.
But...
Really, it's fine!
All right. Good luck, then.
Sure.
I always did my summer homework on the last
day of break in my previous life, too...
How's it going with Fortune Lover?
Making progress?
Uh... I conquered the cocky
prince and the frivolous guy,
but the black-hearted, sadistic prince is pretty tough.
Catarina just keeps getting in the way.
I've already completed all the routes!
What? Already?
You're so quick, Acchan...
There's one route that was really hard, though.
Wanna know which one?
W-Wait, don't! No spoilers!
It was...
Lady Catarina, it's morning.
You need to wake up.
No... I don't wanna hear it...
I don't wanna hear it, I said! No!
Lady Catarina...
Lady Catarina!
O-Oh... Good morning.
Yes, a good morning to you.
I feel like I had a really nostalgic dream...
A dream?
Yeah, the dream I had just now.
I forgot it as soon as I woke up, though.
You've very tired after spending the
whole night doing your homework.
My homework?!
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on